server4sale.com 2013-04-20

# Server4sale - Privacy Policy

Server4Sale offers a range of complete server hosting solutions under the best data center in the world...   
Click here for more...

Our dedicated server means 'All in One'. Our dedicated server is not only an extra feature to your hosting plan, it is the whole solution.... Click here for more...

Server4Sale offers 24/7 Technical Support with many other ways to contact us through emails and direct phone calls...  
Click here for more...

Customer will be legally bound to the our TOS

The customer will be legally bound to the following Privacy Policy,  
Acceptable Use Policy and any other terms and conditions of the  
relevant datacenter of the server that the customer  
orders from Server4Sale.

## PRIVACYPOLICY

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

  * To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to make it easy for you to renew your availed services.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

All clients may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.server4sale.com/tos.html>.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on January 24, 2011

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

www.server4sale.com  
4909 Covewood Court  
Glen Allen VA, 23060   
USA  
1-888-765-7776
